fuller.edu 2013-05-30

# Privacy Policy | Fuller Theological Seminary

Privacy Policy

Fuller Theological Seminary appreciates your interest and use of our web sites.  Since we share your concerns for privacy, this policy was created to inform you about what information we collect about you, how we collect it, use it, disclose it, and your rights regarding information you submit. Your privacy rights are important to us and we will be diligent to safeguard all information that you share with us. This policy discloses the privacy practices of Fuller Theological Seminary regarding its information collection forms at the [_www.fuller.edu_](http://www.fuller.edu/), [_www.guestcenter.com_](http://www.guestcenter.com/), [_www.fullerseminarybookstore.com_](http://www.fullerseminarybookstore.com/), and [_www.fulleronline.org_](http://www.fulleronline.org/) web sites.

 **Collection and Use of Non-personal Information**

Fuller Seminary’s web sites log IP addresses for system administration purposes. These logs may be analyzed to improve the value of the content available and navigational features on these sites. 

Fuller Theological Seminary web sites may log IP addresses and browser types, but will not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session may be tracked but their identity will remain anonymous.  You can browse Fuller Seminary web sites without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit. 

Fuller Theological Seminary uses small files called “cookies” to store and track what you look at when you browse the pages of our web site.  These cookies do not collect personal information, only statistical data that may be analyzed to improve our web sites.  If you are concerned about “cookies”, you can set your browser to review, accept or reject cookies.

 **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

If you enter information on any of Fuller Seminary’s online forms that identifies you, it is considered personal information.  Examples of personal information are your name, gender, postal addresses, social security number, phone numbers, fax numbers, e-mail addresses, credit card number, date of birth, current employment reference names, , citizenship, age, denomination, educational history, references, gift amounts if you are a donor, questions regarding dismissal from previous institutions and felony convictions, and/or religious/ministry autobiography.

The above information is used in several ways: to maintain contact with you, to evaluate for admission, to transact a fee charge and receipt, for authentication purposes to prevent duplication in our data system, seminary event registration, product or service orders, and some is shared with authorized employees and/or agents as needed to provide requested services.  The use of some information may be specified on a particular form.

Some forms establish password-protected accounts.  Please do not share these passwords with anyone to avoid compromising secure access to your personal information.

All information that you submit to our web sites will be treated as confidential.  We do not disclose your information to third parties unless required by law.

 **Correcting, Updating, or Withdrawing Information**

At any time after submitting your information to any Fuller web site form, you may correct, update or withdraw your information.  To do so, please see the relevant contact under “Assistance with Forms” section below.

 **Assistance with Forms**

This privacy policy covers key forms on the Fuller Seminary web site.  Should you need to correct or update data you submitted on any form, opt-out of the submitted form, or have questions regarding a particular form, the following contacts are provided, identified with their online form:

 ** _Admissions Online Application Forms_**

Fuller Theological Seminary uses “CollegeNet” for its online admission application process.  In addition to this privacy policy covering the online application form, you should consult the privacy policy of “CollegeNet” for additional information about privacy protection from this vendor used by Fuller. Contact:  Office of Admissions, [_admissions@fuller.edu_](mailto:adm-intake@fuller.edu), 626-584-5400 

 ** _Alumni Personal Information Form_**

Contact:  Alumni/ae and Church Relations, [_alum-alumni@fuller.edu_](mailto:dev-gifts@dept.fuller.edu), 626-584-5498

 ** _Brehm Center Forms_**

Contact:  Brehm Center, [_brehmcenter@fuller.edu_](mailto:dev-gifts@dept.fuller.edu), 626-304-3789

 ** _Career Services Forms_**

Contact:  Career Services, [_cs@fuller.edu_](mailto:dev-gifts@dept.fuller.edu), 626-584-5358

 ** _Center for Lifeline Learning (CLL)_**

Contact:  Center for Lifeline Learning, [_cll@fuller.edu_](mailto:cll@fuller.edu), 626-584-5669

 ** _Distributed Learning_**

   Contact:  Distributed Learning, [_dl@fuller.edu_](mailto:dl@fuller.edu), 626-584-5266

 ** _Financial Aid Forms_**

Contact:  Office of Student Financial Services, [_sfs-info@fuller.edu_](mailto:sfs-info@fuller.edu), 626-584-5475

 ** _Fuller Online Applicant Form_**

Fuller Theological Seminary utilizes “eCollege” as its delivery system to offer online courses.  This form’s information is shared securely between Fuller Seminary and eCollege to effect the application process.

Contact:  Office of Admissions, [_online_](mailto:admiss@fuller.edu)[ _@fuller.edu_](mailto:admiss@fuller.edu), 626-584-5266

 ** _Office of Korean Doctor of Ministry_**

Contact: Office of Korean Doctor of Ministry, [_kdmin@fuller.edu_](mailto:kdmin@fuller.edu), 626-584-5651

 ** _Office of Development Constituent Update Form_**

Contact:  Office of Development, [_development@fuller.edu_](mailto:dev-gifts@dept.fuller.edu), 626-584-5490

 ** _Office of Development Online Giving Form_**

Contact:  Office of Development, [_development@fuller.edu_](mailto:dev-gifts@dept.fuller.edu), 626-584-5490

 ** _Office of Human Resources Employment Application Form_**

Contact:  Office of Human Resources, [_hr@fuller.edu_](mailto:hr@fuller.edu), 626-584-5454

 ** _Prospective Student Weekend Registration Form_**

Contact:  Office of Admissions, [_admissions@fuller.edu_](mailto:admissions@fuller.edu), 626-584-5400

 **Security**

When users submit their personal information using any form on the Fuller Seminary website, their personal information is scrambled using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet.  Fuller Seminary provides data handling procedures that help protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control.

 **Links**

Our web sites contain links to non-Fuller, external web sites. Any used for forms are secure.  Fuller Theological Seminary’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other external web sites, only to our own web sites as identified above and the secure links to information forms.  Please consult these other external sites regarding their own privacy policies and practices if they collect information from you. 

**Policy Revision and Consent**

Fuller Theological Seminary reserves the right to revise this policy at any time, please check this page periodically for updates.  If revisions are made, they will be posted on this web page.  In using the web sites of Fuller Theological Seminary, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described in this policy. 

**Contact   **   

If you have any questions about this policy, you may contact the Chief Information Officer:

Michael Murray  
Fuller Theological Seminary  
135 N. Oakland Ave.  
Pasadena, CA 91182  
626-584-5219[ _  
mdmurray@fuller.edu_](mailto:mdmurray@fuller.edu)
